Hey everyone welcome to my
YouTube, I was trading below 0 point,
gave a breakout and is
ready to move on the upside after retest, as you
can see here, earlier when
this stock was moving on the upside in the past, it got
resistance and rejection from this very point,
then secondly when it was going to
give a breakout, it got
resistance from this very point, gave a
breakout, it closed at this very point and
moved on the upside and
immediately selling came, then it gave a
breakout from this very point,
it got a rejection here to move on the upside and it had got
multiple rejections here,
which gives a clear
indication that this one is
very important for it,
now it has crossed this point and
given a closing on the upside,
a reversal pattern has also been formed in the monthly time frame,
I told you in my old videos also
that whenever this type of pattern is
formed in the market, then the stock  It
moves very well on the upside and you can clearly see the prediction of a good
return from your stock
here.
This is the formation of an inverted head and shoulders pattern.
This is its left shoulder. This is its
head point. This is its right shoulder. The
breakout has been recorded and it is ready to move on the upside.
Whenever we
analyze a stock in the monthly time frame, we get a clear indication from there as to
where its entry
should be. As is clearly visible here,
its entry point should have been near 1498
and
its stop loss should be near the previous swing level, which is 148.
We can consider its stop loss and move ahead. The
stock is looking very bullish and
can give very good returns on the upside. What should be its target?
Your stock stop loss will be on the previous swing level. As
we calculate the point here and
see, here your ₹1.2 is
coming out, so your minimum
target should be from this breakout level.  It should be exactly ₹1-2.
According to technical analysis, if you look at it,
it will trade exactly near its all-time high.
After that, if you get a target of ₹152, then
you will get the target exactly near the high. It can spend some time
here near the high. As the stock is
looking strong right now, it can spend some time here
and it is possible that
you may get to see a new high by breaking its all-time high. The second thing is
that whenever this type of pattern forms, the
inverted head and shoulders pattern, then
here its head point and
its high point, the neck point,
if we calculate this, then after
breaking the ₹2500000 high,
your target comes out near the round level 1700. The
stock is looking very good in the smaller time frame also. It has given a
breakout in the zone which it tested as resistance multiple times and the entry also looks very good. The
stop loss is also very good.
Similar type of stop loss is placed near the previous swing.
For technical analysis, subscribe to the channel now and
like the video.
That's all for now, thank you.